Privacy Policy
==============

1\. Why we collect your personal information
--------------------------------------------

Personal information is data that can be used to identify you directly or indirectly or to contact you. Our Privacy Policy covers all personal information that you voluntarily submit to us and that we obtain from our partners. This Privacy Policy does not apply to anonymized data, as it cannot be used to identify you.

You may be asked to provide personal information anytime you are in contact with SwapSwop. We may use your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, SwapSwop will not give, sell, rent or loan any personal information to any third party.

2\. What type of information we collect
---------------------------------------

Any information that we collect is necessary either to provide you the services or to comply with legal regulations and legislation. You may refuse to provide us with some types of the personal information requested, but in this case, we may not be able to ensure that the service works properly for you and that all services are available.

Depending on the service you wish to use, we may collect the following types of information:

* Full name, date of birth, nationality, place of birth, age, phone number, home address, and/or email.
* Tax number, passport number, driver’s license details, national identity card details, photograph identification cards.
* Bank account details, payment card details, transaction history, trading data, and/or tax identification.
* Survey responses, the information provided to our support team, public social networking posts, authentication data, security questions, user ID, other data collected via cookies and similar technologies.

3\. How your personal information is used
-----------------------------------------

The main purpose for collecting personal information is to provide you with a secure, and convenient experience. How this information can be used:

to create, develop, operate, deliver, and improve the services that you use on SwapSwop website;

to comply with the legal requirements and applicable legislation;

for loss prevention and anti-fraud purposes.

4\. Additional information from external sources
------------------------------------------------

We may obtain information about you from third party sources as required or permitted by applicable law, such as public databases, credit bureaus, ID verification partners, resellers and channel partners, joint marketing partners, and social media platforms. We obtain such information to comply with our legal obligations, such as anti-money laundering laws. Our lawful basis for processing such data is compliance with legal obligations. In some cases, we may process additional data about you to ensure our Services are not used fraudulently or for other illicit activities.

5\. Automatically collected information
---------------------------------------

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system, and browser type, for system administration, problem-solving, and service improvement. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns and does not identify any individual.

6\. Cookies
-----------

One of the ways we collect data about your use of the SwapSwop service is through the use of cookies. It helps us with the analysis of the visits to our services and helps us to deliver a better product. You can manage cookies through the settings of your internet browser. You can have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, delete individual cookies or delete all cookies.

7\. Sharing personal information with other parties
---------------------------------------------------

SwapSwop may share your information in the following circumstances:

We share your information with third-party identity verification services in order to prevent fraud. This allows SwapSwop to confirm your identity by comparing the information you provide us to public records and other third party databases.

We may share your information with service providers under contract who help with parts of our business operations such as Cryptocurrency exchange service, Cryptocurrency purchase and sell service. We ensure that any such third party is aware of our obligations under this Privacy Policy and our contracts prohibit them to sell your information to anyone else.

We may share your information with financial institutions with which we partner to process payments you have authorized.

We may share your information with law enforcement or regulatory agencies, as may be required by law.

8\. Protection of the personal information
------------------------------------------

We will not permit any third parties to contact you directly on an unsolicited basis in relation to their own products or services. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others. You should never disclose your account password to unauthorized parties. We use certain security measures to help keep your personal information safe, but we cannot guarantee that these measures will stop any users try to get around the privacy or security settings on the Website through unforeseen and/or illegal activity.

Exchange cryptocurrency **anonymously**

### Company

### Legal

### Support

### Resources

SwapSwop OÜ. Harju maakond, Tallinn, Kesklinna linnaosa, Vesivärava tn 50, 201, 10152.  
Company Registry Code: 16184686.
